Wisconsin Unemployment Compensation Department Miscellaneous Tables 5379
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wisconsin Unemployment Compensation Department Miscellaneous Tables
1953-1965
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wisconsin Unemployment Compensation Department
5379
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Consists of unemployment compenstation statistics from the Statistical Department of the Industrial Commission of Wisconsin.
5620260
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 08, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of tables of unemployment compenstation statistics from the Statistical Department of the Industrial Commission of Wisconsin. The tables are arranged in alphabetical order by keyword.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5319: New York State Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board Decisions 5376: New York State Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board Decisions
Unemployment insurance -- Wisconsin; Wisconsin.; Wisconsin. Unemployment Compensation Department
5620260
- Appeal tribunal, 1955-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Benefits paid in Wisconsin, 1954-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Cases pending, 1955-1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Consecutive weeks, 1955-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Ex-servicemen and veterans, 1955-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Experience, 1954-1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- First payments, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Industrial commission decisions, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Industry group classification, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Initial determinations, 1955-1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Number of covered workers, by month, 1954-1961 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Promptness, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Size of reporting unit, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Summary of benefits, 1955-1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Type of payroll, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- UCFE claims, 1955-1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Scope and Contents
  Unemployment compensation for federal civil employees
- Wages paid, by quarter, 1953-1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)